A Finding Aid to the E. P. (Edgar Preston) and Constance Richardson papers, 1814-1996, bulk 1921-1996, in the Archives of American Art
Archives of American Art
- Artist-Subject files, 1923-1982; Series 6; Archival Resource Key; 7 Linear feet Boxes 17-24
  - Hopkins, John Henry, 1931-1940; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 67)
  - Hopper, Edward, circa 1934-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 68)
  - Hoppner, John, 1948; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 69)
  - Hotchkiss, Thomas M. circa 1834, circa 1934-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 70)
  - Houdon, Jean-Antoine, 1963-1970; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 71)
  - Hovenden, Thomas, circa 1934-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 72)
  - H; Hudson, Thomas; Hughes, Robert Ball 1806-1868, circa 1947-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 73)
  - Hudson Valley, Upper XVIII Century, 1975; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 74)
  - Humor & Caricature, American, 1933-1962; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 75)
  - Hunt, William Morris 1824-1879, 1967-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 76)
  - Huntington, Daniel 1816-1896, circa 1973; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - American Indian, 1958-1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Ingersoll, Jared, 1967-1971; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Ingham, Charles C., circa 1934-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Ingres, Jean-Auguste-Dominique, 1946-1951; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Inman, Henry, circa 1934-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Inness, George 1825-1897, 1976; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Irving, Washington - Portraits, 1965-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Italian, Dutch, circa 1934-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Jackson, Andrew, 1958; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Jamaica, 1968-1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Jarvis, John Wesley 1780-1839, 1967-1976; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Jefferson, Thomas, 1961-1975; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Jennys, William, circa 1934-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - John, Augustus, circa 1934-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Johnson, David 1827-1908, circa 1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Johnson, Eastman, 1947-1980; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Johnston, David Claypoole, 1945, 1973; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Johnston, John 1752-1818, 1959; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Jones, Samuel, circa 1934-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Jovett, Matthew, 1976-1981; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - K; Keene, Charles S. 1823-1891; Kent, Rockwell; King, Samuel 1748-9-1819; Koehler, Robert; Kuhn, Justus; Engelhardt; Kuhn, Walt; Kuniyoshi, Yasuo, 1937-circa 1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - Kelloy, Miner K. 1814-1899, 1960-1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - Kennedy, David J., 1966-1975; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - Kensett, John F., 1967-1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - King, Charles B. 1785-1862, 1948-1972; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 26)
  - Knapton, George, 1958; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 27)
  - Kneller, Sir Godfrey, circa 1934-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 28)
  - Kosciusko, Thaddeus, 1974-1975; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 29)
  - Krimmel, John Lewis, circa 1934-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 30)
  - LaFarge, John, 1962-1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 31)
  - L; Lambdin, George C.; Latrobe, Benjamin Henry; Lawson, Ernest; Le Clear, Thomas 1818-1852; Lu, Joseph, circa 1934-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 32)
  - Lane, Fitzhugh, 1944-1974; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 33)
  - LaSalle, Rene de - Portrait of Aram, 1949-1950; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 34)
  - Early Landscape - Minor, circa 1934-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 35)
  - Lauren Hill Cemetary, circa 1934-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 36)
  - Lawrence, Charles B. circa 1790/93 - after 1846, 1968-1973; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 37)
  - Lawrence, Sir Thomas, circa 1934-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 38)
  - Leitch, Thomas active 1773-1774, 1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 39)
  - Lely, Sir Peter, circa 1934-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 40)
  - L; LeMoyne, Jacques; Le Serrurier, James; Levine, Jack; Lewis, Edmund Darch 1837-1910; Library Company; Luks, George, circa 1943-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 41)
  - Leslie, Charles Robert 1794-1859, 1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 42)
  - Leutze, Emmanuel, 1971; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 43)
  - Lincoln - Paintings, 1975; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 44)
  - Lincoln - Sculpture, 1947-1958; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 45)
  - Lindstrom, Peter Martenson, 1979; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 46)
  - Louisiana, 1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 47)
  - Louvre Exhibit - Boston, 1981-1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 48)
  - M; McCloskey, William John; Madison, James; Malbone, Robert Bolton 1777-1807; Marsh, Reginald 1878-1954; Marshall, Ben; Mayr, Christian 1805-1850; Medals, circa 1934-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 49)
  - McEntee, Jervis 1829-1891, 1976; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 50)
  - McIlworth, Thomas 1757-1767, 1972; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 51)
  - McIntire, Samuel 1757-1814, circa 1943-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 52)
  - Mallett, circa 1934-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 53)
  - Manship, Paul 1885-1966, 1947; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 54)
  - Manet, Edouard, 1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 55)
  - Mare, John 1739-circa 1795, 1955, 1973; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 56)
  - Marin, John, circa 1934-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 57)
  - Marine & River Scenes, circa 1934-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 58)
  - Martin, Homer D., circa 1934-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 59)
  - Mason, Sanford, circa 1934-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 60)
  - Mason Children 1670, 1934; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 61)
  - Matteson, Tomkins H., 1961; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 62)
  - Maya, 1964-1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 63)
  - Mayer, Frank Blackwell, 1976; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 64)
  - M; Melchers, Gari 1860-1932; Mercier; Miartani, P; Millet, Francis Davis 1846-1912; Millmore, Martin; Molarsky, Maurice, circa 1934-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 65)
  - Metcalf, Willard L., 1976; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 66)
  - Metropolitan Museum of Art, New York, 1972-1977; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 67)
  - Middle States - Unknown, 1967-1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 68)
  - Mignot, Louis Remy 1831-1870, circa 1934-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 69)
  - Miller, Alfred J., 1943-1948; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 70)
  - Miniatures, 1946-1964, 1980; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 71)
  - Missouri, 1947; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 72)
  - "Modernization of the City, 1825-1841" by Nicholas B. Wainwright, 1970; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 73)
  - Monamy, [Peter], circa 1935-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 74)
  - Monet, Claude, 1953; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 75)
  - Moran, Thomas 1837-1926, 1972-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 76)
  - M; Morisot, Berthe; Morton, John Ludlow 1794-1871; Moses, Grandma; Moultrhop, Reuben; Myers, Jerome, circa 1934-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 77)
  - Mormons, circa 1924-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 78)
  - Morse, John D., 1972-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 79)
  - Morse, Samuel Finkley Beeze 1791-1872, 1952-1977; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Mount Vernon Lithographs 1858-1859, 1972; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Mount, William s. 1807-1868, circa 1934-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Murray, Samuel, 1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Museums & Galleries, 1951, 1963; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Nahl, Charles Christian, 1944; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - N; Nast, Thomas; Negus, Nathan; Newell, Peter 1862-1924; Newman, Robert Loftin 1835-1912; New Mexico; New Orleans - Portrait Painting in; Nollekens, Joseph Frans, circa 1934-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - National Gallery of Art, 1959-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Neagle, John 1796-2865, 1972-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Nebraska, 1966-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Neuville, Baroness Anne de 1779-1849, 1974; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1976-1980; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Olmec, 1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Otis, Bass, 1977; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Page, William, 1938-1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 15-16)
  - Page, William - Artists' Family, 1948-1954; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - P; Parrish, Maxfield; Pennington, Harper, 1970; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Paul, Jeremiah, 1959-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Pelham, Peter, 1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - People, 1971-1979; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - Peto, John F., 1965-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - Philadelphia: Print Conference 1973, 1972-1977; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - Phillips, Charles; Pollock, Jackson, circa 1934-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 24)
  - Pierpont Limner - Painter of the Pierpont Portrait, 1958; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 25)
  - Pine, Robert Edge - George Read Portrait, 1963-1976; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 26)
  - Pitts, Lendall, circa 1934-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 27)
  - Polk, Charles Peale Polk, 1975-1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 28)
  - Portraits of American Interest in Britain, 1971; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 29)
  - Powers, Hiram 1805-1873, 1960-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 30)
  - Pratt, Matthew, 1967-1974; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 31)
  - Prendergast, Maurice, 1968-1975; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 32)
  - Pringle, James 1827-, 1944, 1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 33)
  - Prints - American, 1939-1973; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 34)
  - Prints - Historical, 1950-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 35)
  - Print - Four American Political, 1974; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 36)
  - Quidor, John 1801-1881, 1943-1944; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 37)
  - R; Ramage, John 1763-1802; Ramsey, Milne 1846-1915; Read, Thomas Buchanan 1822-1872; Remington, Frederic 1861-1909; Richardson, J., circa 1934-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 38)
  - Ramsey, Allen, circa 1934-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 39)
  - Rannay, William Tylee, 1948; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 40)
  - Republic, The, circa 1934-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 41)
  - Reynolds, Joshua, 1955-1956; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 42)
  - Riboni, Giacinto, circa 1934-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 43)
  - Rimmer, William 1816-1879, 1966-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 44)
  - Rindisbacher, Peter, 1970; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 45)
  - Ring, Alice Blair, 1977; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 46)
  - Rivera, Diego, 1959-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 47)
  - Rivera in Detroit, 1930-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 48)
  - Robertson, Walter circa Mid 18th Century to 1802, 1957; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 49)
  - R; Robertson, W.; Robinson, Theodore 1852-1896; Rocsen, Severin; Rogers, Randolph 1825-1892; Romans, Bernard, 1945-1973; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 50)
  - Rolshoven, Julius, 1947; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 51)
  - Romanticism I 1775-1794, circa 1934-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 52)
  - Romanticism III 1815-1834, 1950-1975; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 53)
  - Romney, George, 1947; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 54)
  - Roseland, Harry 1868-1950, 1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 55)
  - R; Rosin, Harry; Rossetti, Dante Gabriel; Russell, Charles M., circa 1934-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 56)
  - Rossiter, Thomas P. 1818-1871, 1944; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 57)
  - Rowland, Benjamin 1904-1972, 1967-1972; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 58)
  - Ruggles, Carl 1876-1971, 1964-1974; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 59)
  - Rush, William 1756-1883, 1970-1980; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 60)
  - Ryder, Albert Pinkham, circa 1934-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 61)
  - St. Gaudens, Augustus 1848-1907, 1972; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 62)
  - Saint-Memin, Fevret 1770-1852, 1968-1974; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 63)
  - S; Salmon, Robert 1775-1850; Sandby, Thomas; Sargent, Henry; Schragvosh, Charles; Scott, Julian; Sharp, William, circa 1934-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 64)
  - Sargent, John Singer, 1948-1974; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 65)
  - Savage, Edward, 1954-1972; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Schenectady Residents - Portraits 1715-1750, 1962-1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Scotland 1700-1750, circa 1934-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Scotland 1750-1800, 1971; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Scotland XVII Century, circa 1934-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Scotland 1850-1900, 1949; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Sculpture XVIII, 1944-1947; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Sculpture - Primitive & Folk Traditions, 1943-1956; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - 1700-1750, 1957-1980; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - 1725-1744, 1971; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Unknown 1750-1775, 1979; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Shahn, Ben, 1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Sharples, James, 1975; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Shaw, Horatio, circa 1934-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Shaw, Joshua 1776-1860, 1961-1981; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - S; Sheeler, Charles; Simon, Herman; Smith, Frank Hill; Smith, Thomas; Sonntag, W.L. 1822-1900; Strickland, William, circa 1934-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Ship's Carvings, 1954; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Ship's Carvings - Great Lakes, 1954; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - Sloan, John, circa 1934-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - Smibert, Philip Livingston, Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - Smith, Russell 1812-1896, 1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - Smith, Xanthus, 1976-1977; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - South Carolina, 1967-1970; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - Spencer, Lily Martin, 1943; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 24)
  - Stanley, John Mix, 1960-1979; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 25)
  - Stella, Joseph, 1957; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 26)
  - Steward, Joseph 1753-1822, 1972-1975; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 27)
  - Strother, David (Porte Crayon), 1958; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 28)
  - Story, Julian 1857-1919, 1948; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 29)
  - Street, Robert 1796-1865, 1968, 1981-1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 30)
  - Stuart, Gilbert 1755-1828, 1957-1981; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 31)
  - Stuart, Gilbert - English & Irish, 1976-1977; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 32)
  - Stuart, Gilbert vs John E. Swords 1802, 1967-1976; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 33)
  - Stuart, Gilbert - Washington, 1946-1980; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 34)
  - Stuart, Jane, 1943, 1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 35)
  - Stubbs, George, 1953; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 36)
  - Sullivan, William, circa 1934-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 37)
  - Sully, James C., 1970; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 38)
  - Sully, Thomas, 1944-1945, 1971-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 39)
  - Swan, James, 1975; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 40)
  - Tait, Arthur F. 1819-1905, 1945-1946; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 41)
  - Technology - "the Exhilartion of Early American Technology" by Brooke Hindle, 1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 42)
  - T; Terry, Luther; Thayer, Abbott 1849-1921; Thompson, Jerome; Thornhill, Sir Jams 1676-1734; tilyard, Philip; Tissot, James; Tobey, Mark; Tripoli Monument, circa 1934-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 43)
  - Theus, Jeremiah, 1951-1971; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 44)
  - Thompson, Cephas G., circa 1934-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 45)
  - Tikal, 1962-1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 46)
  - Tintoretto, circa 1934-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 47)
  - Traquair, James, 1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 48)
  - Trompe L'Oeil, 1981; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 49)
  - Troye, Edward, 1944, 1979; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 50)
  - Trumbull, John 1756-1843, 1949, 1967-1972; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 51)
  - Trumbull & LaTrobe - Portrait Drawing of Jefferson, 1975-1976; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 52)
  - Turner, Joseph Mallord William, 1947-1950; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 53)
  - Twatchman, John H. 1853-1902, circa 1934-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 54)
  - XX Century - 1st Generation 1865-1884, circa 1934-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 55)
  - XX Century - 2nd Generation 1885-1904, 1973-1979; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 56)
  - XX Century - 3rd Generation 1905-1924, 1968-1980; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 57)
  - Tyler, William R. 1825-1896 (Mrs. Copeland's Painting), 1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 58)
  - Ulrich, Charles Frederick 1858-1909, circa 1934-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 59)
  - Unknown, 1923-1981; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 60)
  - Van Cortlandt Limner, 1972; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 61)
  - V; Van Der Lyn, Pieter; Van Dyke, James; Verelst, Simon Pieters; Volk, Douglas; Volk, Loenara 1828-1895, 1944-1957; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 62)
  - Vanderlyn, John 1775-1852, 1947-1981; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 63)
  - Van Dyck - English Period, 1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 64)
  - Van Dyck, Anton - Helian & Flemish, 1957; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 65)
  - Vedder, Elihu 1836-1923, 1960-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 66)
  - Vulliamy & Cipriani; G.B. Clock, 1956; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 67)
  - Waldo, Samuel Lovett, 1968-1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - W; Walker, William A. 1838-1921; Watson, John; Waugh, Frederick J 1861-1940; Weber, Max 1881-; Websted, Daniel; Ward, J.Q.A. 1830-1910, circa 1934-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - War, 1977-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Washington, George, 1968-1979; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Washington - Contemporary but not From Life, 1971-1974; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - George Washington - "The Evidence of the Portraits," 1976, Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Mrs. Washington, circa 1934-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Washington - Mount Vernon, 1971-1975; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Washington - Not Contemporary, 1968-1977; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Washington - 1772, circa 1934-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Weidner, Roswell, 1981; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Weir, Robert W. 1803-1889, 1977; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Wertmuller, Albert, 1975; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - West, Benjamin, 1936-1979; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - West, William E. 1788-1857, 1960-1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - W; Wheatly, Francis; winner, W.E.; Wood, Grant; Wood, Joseph; Wright, George; Wright, Patience; Wyeth, N.C.; Wood, Thomas Waterman 1823-1903, circa 1934-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Whistler, James McNeill, 1927-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - Whittredge, T. Worthington 1820-1900, 1943-1972; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - W R pinxit 1674 [Utica], 1973; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - Williams, William, 1951-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - Williams, William J. 1759-1823, 1969-1971; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - Williams, William 1758-1797 No. 4, 1968, 1977; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 22)
  - Wilson, Alexander, 1944-1950; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 23)
  - Wilson, Benjamin, 1946-1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 24)
  - Wilson, Richard, 1948; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 25)
  - Winstanley, William, 1968-1974; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 26)
  - Wollaston, John, 1971-1977; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 27)
  - Woodville, [Richard Caton], circa 1934-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 28)
  - Wright, Joseph 1756-1793, 1965-1976; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 29)
  - Wright, Thomas of Derby, 1950; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 30)
  - Wyant, Alexander 1836-1892, circa 1934-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 31)
  - Wyeth, Andrew, 1938-1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 32-35)
  - Young, Mahonri 1877-1957, circa 1934-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 36)
  - Zoffany, Johann, 1945; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 37)
- Collector files, 1921-1981; Series 7; Archival Resource Key; 0.6 Linear feet Boxes 24-25
  Collector files contain reference material, such as printed materials, photographs, notes, authentications, and some correspondence about art collectors and their collections including Lamont du Pont Copeland, Michael W. Freeman, Nelson Rockefeller, Mr. and Mrs. Joseph Allen, and the Marquis de Somerlous.
  - American Collectors 20th Century, 1961-1975; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 38)
  - Biggs, Sewell C., 1976-1979; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 39)
  - Bonaparte, Joseph, 1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 40)
  - Bryan, Thomas J., 1971; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 41)
  - Byrd, William, circa 1963; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 42)
  - Carey, Henry Charles, 1966-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 43)
  - Clarke, Thomas B., 1935; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 44)
  - Collectors & Collecting, 1949-1971; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 45)
  - Congdon, C.S., circa 1921; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 46)
  - Copeland, Lamont du Pont, 1962-1970; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 47)
  - Fisher, W.A., 1961; Archival Resource Key (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Forest, Edwin, 1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Freeman, Michael W., circa 1955; Archival Resource Key (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Harrison, Joseph Jr., 1971-1972; Archival Resource Key (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Hart, Charles Henry, 1972-1976; Archival Resource Key (Box 25, Folder 5)